Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Project Files, 1965-1995; Series IX
  - Mark Rother, 1978-1994; Subseries 16
    - Transportation
      - Peninsula Development Association, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 654/9)
      - Seattle and North Coast Railroad, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 654/10)
      - Seattle and North Coast Railroad, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 655/1)
      - Seattle Transit Proposal, 1984 (Box-folder 655/2)
      - Snohomish Co. Community Transit, 1987 (Box-folder 655/3)
      - Surface Transportation Assistance Act of 1991, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 655/4)
      - Tri- State Highway 101 Council, 1986 (Box-folder 655/5)
      - Washington State Ferry System, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 655/6)
      - Washington State Ferry System, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 655/7)
  - Dee Dee Sigler, 1979-1988; Subseries 17
    Note: Includes projects related to children and parenthood issues; civil rights; education; legal issues; and the U.S. Navy.
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/1)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/2)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/3)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/4)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/5)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/6)
    - Children/ Parenthood Issues, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 656/7)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/8)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/9)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/10)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/11)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/12)
    - Civil Rights, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 656/13)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/1)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/2)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/3)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/4)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/5)
    - Civil Rights, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/6)
    - Constituents, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/7)
    - Constituents, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/8)
    - Constituents, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 657/9)
    - Education, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 657/10)
    - Education, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 657/11)
    - Education, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 657/12)
    - Education, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 657/13)
    - Education, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 658/1)
    - Education, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 658/2)
    - English Language Initiative, 1985 (Box-folder 658/3)
    - FmHA Tax Bill, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 658/4)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/5)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/6)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/7)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/8)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/9)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/10)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/11)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/12)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/13)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/14)
    - Legal Issues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 658/15)
    - Legal Issues, 1985 (Box-folder 659/1)
    - U.S. Navy, 1985 (Box-folder 659/2)
  - Nancy Wampler, 1984-1985; Subseries 18
    Note: Includes projects related to health care issues.
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/1)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/2)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/3)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/4)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/5)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/6)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/7)
    - Health Care, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 660/8)
  - John Wilson, 1979; Subseries 19
    Note: Includes projects related to the Skagit Nuclear Power Project.
    - Skagit Nuclear Power Project, 1979 (Box-folder 661/1)
    - Skagit Nuclear Power Project, 1979 (Box-folder 661/2)
    - Skagit Nuclear Power Project, 1979 (Box-folder 661/3)
    - Skagit Nuclear Power Project, 1979 (Box-folder 661/4)
  - Miscellaneous Projects, 1977-1994; Subseries 20
    Note: Projects in this section range widely in topic and are arranged alphabetically.
    - A.I.D.S. Problem, 1984 (Box-folder 662/1)
    - American Broadcasting Letter 8/11/81; Program "Viewpoint" Transcript, 1981, 1984 (Box-folder 662/2)
    - Annual Report of the Viacom Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 662/3)
    - Al's Position on Tax Reform, Undated (Box-folder 662/4)
    - Al Swift-- Energy and Commerce Committee Assignments, Undated (Box-folder 662/5)
    - Areas of Responsibility, 1981 (Box-folder 662/6)
    - AWPPW-- Bosworth, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 662/7)
    - Bellevue Commercial Communications System, 1979 (Box-folder 662/8)
    - Bellingham-Alaska Marine Highway, 1979 (Box-folder 662/9)
    - Bellingham Issue Files, 1980-1994 (Box-folder 662/10)
    - Border Issues Local Bellingham, 1979-1993 (Box-folder 662/11)
    - Border, Pre-1992, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 662/12)
    - Bosnian Situation-- Correspondence, Public Affairs, and Congressional Papers, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 662/13)
    - Buse Lumber, 1979 (Box-folder 662/14)
    - City College, 1979 (Box-folder 663/1)
    - Coast Guard Buoy Chain Acquisition, Undated (Box-folder 663/2)
    - Common Cause Memo, Sept. 9, 1981, Problem of Independent Expenditures, 1981 (Box-folder 663/3)
    - City of Seattle, 1979 (Box-folder 663/4)
    - Customs Users Fees, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 663/5)
    - Dalton 1980, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 663/6)
    - Daylight Savings Time, 1985 (Box-folder 663/7)
    - DC Cosponsor/Dear Colleague, 1993 (Box-folder 663/8)
    - DC Statehood Pro., 1993 (Box-folder 663/9)
    - Defense Base Cuts, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 663/10)
    - Du-Cap Wiztronics F.C.C., 1979 (Box-folder 663/11)
    - Energy and Commerce Committee, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 663/12)
    - Energy, Conservation, and Power Oversight Hearings-- NRC Licensing Board, 1982 (Box-folder 663/13)
    - FEMA, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 664/1)
    - Ferndale Library, 1979 (Box-folder 664/2)
    - Flood, 1979 (Box-folder 664/3)
    - Foreign Hunger, 1985 (Box-folder 664/4)
    - Foreign Relations-- Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 664/5)
    - Gannett News Service, 1981 (Box-folder 664/6)
    - Gas Allocations, 1979 (Box-folder 664/7)
    - GATT/Fast Track, 1991 (Box-folder 664/8)
    - Graham Hollingsworth of Kirkland GSA Contract LANCS Ind., 1980 (Box-folder 664/9)
    - Granite Falls Water System, 1979 (Box-folder 664/10)
    - Harbor Airlines, 1981 (Box-folder 664/11)
    - Highway 101 Project, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 664/12)
    - Housing/Urban Development-- Mt. Vernon, 1980 (Box-folder 664/13)
    - Initiative 404-- Coalition for An Independent Redistricting Commission, 1981 (Box-folder 664/14)
    - Interchange '93, 1993 (Box-folder 664/15)
    - Issue Replies and Form Letters, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 664/16)
    - Issues: Agricultural Trade, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 665/1)
    - Issues: Foreign Matters, 1991 (Box-folder 665/2)
    - Issues: Marine/Fisheries, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 665/3)
    - Issues: National Health Care and Insurance, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 665/4)
    - Issues: Social Security, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 665/5)
    - Issues: Trade, 1991 (Box-folder 665/6)
    - Lake Hancock Bombing Range, 1979 (Box-folder 665/7)
    - Local Bellingham USFS Issues, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 665/8)
    - L-Project Newspaper/Broadcast Cross-Ownership, 1980 (Box-folder 665/9)
    - Magnetic Energy Machine, 1985 (Box-folder 665/10)
    - Marine Resource Company (Jim Talbott), 1979 (Box-folder 665/11)
    - Marysville School District, 1979 (Box-folder 665/12)
    - Mother Joseph Project, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 665/13)
    - Mt. St. Helens Bill, 1982 (Box-folder 665/14)
    - NAS Whidbey Local Issues Bellingham, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 666/1)
    - Natural Fibers International, 1979 (Box-folder 666/2)
    - Navy Use/ Tax Issue, 1979 (Box-folder 666/3)
    - NHTSA Stuff, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 666/4)
    - Office Files-- Everett, 1979-1994 (Box-folder 666/5)
    - Office Files-- Everett, 1979-1994 (Box-folder 667/1)
    - Passage Foundation, 1979 (Box-folder 667/2)
    - Planned Parenthood of Snohomish County, 1979 (Box-folder 667/3)
    - Plywood Tarriffs, 1978 (Box-folder 667/4)
    - Press Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 667/5)
    - Press Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 668/1)
    - Projects, 1977-1994 (Box-folder 668/2)
    - Projects, 1980 (Box-folder 669/1)
    - Project(s)-- Bellingham Chamber "Energy Conservation Task Force", 1979 (Box-folder 669/2)
    - Project(s)-- Catholic Family and Children's Services Facility, 1980 (Box-folder 669/3)
    - Project(s)-- Log Exports-Mail, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 669/4)
    - Project(s)-- Office of Civil Rights Compliance Review, 1979 (Box-folder 669/5)
    - Project(s)-- Nichols Boats-Whidbey Island, 1979 (Box-folder 669/6)
    - Project(s)-- San Juan Emergency, 1980 (Box-folder 669/7)
    - Project(s)-- St. Edwards Park, 1979 (Box-folder 669/8)
    - Project(s)-- Washington State Employment Security Dept., 1979 (Box-folder 669/9)
    - Project(s)-- Whidbey Island, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 669/10)
    - Project(s)-- Y.A.C.C.- Peabody, 1979 (Box-folder 669/11)
    - Public Works Hearing-- Seattle, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 669/12)
    - Public Works Issues, 1991 (Box-folder 669/13)
    - Puget Power Bear Creek Project Letter, 5/15/1981 (Box-folder 669/14)
    - Puget Sound Tankers, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 669/15)
    - P--Washington State, 1980 (Box-folder 670/1)
    - Redistricting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 670/2)
    - Resolution Trust Corporation, 1991 (Box-folder 670/3)
    - Sewers, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 670/4)
    - Skagit County Day Care, 1979 (Box-folder 670/5)
    - Skagit Regional Planning Council, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 670/6)
    - Skagit Valley College, 1980 (Box-folder 670/7)
    - Skagit Valley PACCAR, 1979 (Box-folder 670/8)
    - Small Cities Seminar, 1979 (Box-folder 670/9)
    - Snohomish Basin Coordinating Council, 1980 (Box-folder 670/10)
    - Snohomish County LEAA, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 670/11)
    - Snohomish Surface Water Program, 1979 (Box-folder 670/12)
    - Sol Duc Name Issue, 1991 (Box-folder 670/13)
    - South Terminal Project, 1979 (Box-folder 670/14)
    - Southern Pacific Communications Co., 1981 (Box-folder 670/15)
    - Space/Transportation, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 670/16)
    - Stanwood/Camano News, 1994 (Box-folder 671/1)
    - Swinonomish Channel Bridge, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 671/2)
    - Synthetic Oil/Alternative Energy Sources, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 671/3)
    - Taiwan Aerospace Issue, 1992 (Box-folder 671/4)
    - Tax Bill, 1981 (Box-folder 671/5)
    - Thank You-- Received, 1981 (Box-folder 671/6)
    - Travel-Trip Info., 1981-1982 (Box-folder 671/7)
    - Trumpeter Swans on Barney Lake, 1981 (Box-folder 671/8)
    - Tulalip Indians Ordinance #53, 1981 (Box-folder 671/9)
    - UDAG, 1984 (Box-folder 671/10)
    - Uniflite, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 672/1)
    - Victoria/EPA/State, 1991 (Box-folder 672/2)
    - Washington State Ad Hoc Water Resources Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 672/3)
    - Washington State Associate of Prosecuting Attorneys, 1979 (Box-folder 672/4)
    - Washington State Collectors Association, 1981 (Box-folder 672/5)
    - Weyerhaueser, 1979 (Box-folder 672/6)
    - Weyerhaueser Closure, circa 1992 (Box-folder 672/7)
    - Whatcom/Work Incentive Program grant, 1979 (Box-folder 672/8)
    - White House Conference On Families, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 672/9)
    - Wilderness Protection Act, 1982 (Box-folder 672/10)
    - Working Papers for Legislative Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 672/11)
    - Y.A.C.C, 1980 (Box-folder 672/12)
    - Yakima River Basin Enhancement Project, 1978 (Box-folder 672/13)